Register of the Arnold Ellsworth True papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Audiovisual File, circa 1886-1979 (Boxes 14-16)
  - Two sound discs, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    Includes a Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace recording of speeches by Arnold Ellsworth True, former South Vietnamese Ambassador Tran Van Dinh, and Senator Thruston B. Morton; and a World Peace Broadcasting Foundation recording of speech by Senator Wayne Morse.
  - Four sound tape reels, circa 1967-1970 (Box 16)
    Includes speeches by Arnold Ellsworth True, an interview with True and Norman Mailer, and Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace radio commercial messages.
  - Five sound cassettes, circa 1971-1977 (Box 16)
    Includes speeches by Arnold Ellsworth True and a radio interview with True and Studs Terkel.
- Declassified U.S. Government Records, 1942, 1944 (Box 15)
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder chronologically by date of creation.
  - 2016 February release of records, 1942, 1944 (Box-folder 15: 5)
    United States Navy memoranda, report, and correspondence relating to naval action and citation recommendations, particularly in relation to the sinking of the U.S.S. Hammann.